{
  "type": "multiple-choice",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "あか",
      "choices": {
        "1": "blue",
        "2": "purple",
        "3": "red",
        "4": "black"
      },
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "きいろ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "purple",
        "2": "white",
        "3": "black",
        "4": "yellow"
      },
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "しろ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "white",
        "2": "red",
        "3": "blue",
        "4": "black"
      },
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "くろ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "pink",
        "2": "grey",
        "3": "grey",
        "4": "black"
      },
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "むらさき",
      "choices": {
        "1": "grey",
        "2": "purple",
        "3": "pink",
        "4": "blue"
      },
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "あお",
      "choices": {
        "1": "grey",
        "2": "blue",
        "3": "pink",
        "4": "purple"
      },
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "みどり",
      "choices": {
        "1": "grey",
        "2": "green",
        "3": "brown",
        "4": "orange"
      },
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "はいいろ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "brown",
        "2": "black",
        "3": "red",
        "4": "grey"
      },
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "ちゃいろ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "brown",
        "2": "red",
        "3": "white",
        "4": "orange"
      },
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "おれんじ",
      "choices": {
        "1": "brown",
        "2": "grey",
        "3": "orange",
        "4": "blue"
      },
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "ぴんく",
      "choices": {
        "1": "blue",
        "2": "white",
        "3": "pink",
        "4": "brown"
      },
      "answer": "3"
    }
  ]
}
